<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gus Perez</title>
    <link>http://gusperez.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gus Perez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 14:19:04 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://gusperez.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My PRK Journey</title>
      <link>http://gusperez.com/blog/2022-11-13_my-prk-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 14:19:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gusperez.com/blog/2022-11-13_my-prk-journey/</guid>
      
        <description>These are a couple of posts I’ve kept from my old blog that folks found helpful, so I figured I’d repost them here. Also added a brief update 10+ years post surgery.
July 27, 2011 It’s been almost eight months since I underwent Photorefractive Keratectomy (PRK) eye surgery to finally get rid of my glasses/contacts. It’s similar to the seemingly more common Lasik except for how your cornea gets exposed to the laser (at least that’s how I understand it).</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gusperez.com/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gusperez.com/art/</guid>
      
        <description>Art I used to love to draw when I was a kid, but I&amp;rsquo;ve failed to keep it going. I like to think I will someday. In the meantime, I&amp;rsquo;ve shared a few examples from years past here.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gusperez.com/maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gusperez.com/maker/</guid>
      
        <description>Maker stuff I like making stuff. Mostly into woodworking but also dabble with 3d printing and using lasers to cut stuff with our Glowforge. This is something that my wife and I have ended up doing together a lot more over time. You can follow our journey (pretty much from the start) here.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gusperez.com/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gusperez.com/music/</guid>
      
        <description>Guitar I created GuitarTube.org in 2016. Some folks have found it useful, so I&amp;rsquo;m keeping it around. Still may do more, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also been transcribing songs I enjoy more and more over the years and sharing them on Ultimate Guitar and some on Soundslice.
9U5P I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to get around to recording more and will share that under the 9U5P moniker. See more over on Spotify and other streaming services.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gusperez.com/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gusperez.com/photography/</guid>
      
        <description>Photography Haven&amp;rsquo;t been doing as much as I used to, but you can check out some photos on flickr and 500px.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://gusperez.com/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gusperez.com/software/</guid>
      
        <description>Software Windows Lots of stuff over the years, much of which isn&amp;rsquo;t all that useful nowadays. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list of app names and I&amp;rsquo;ve provided links to GitHub repos for any that I shared there: Wordy, Peekify, TickTalker, DeskTips, Clipboard Snagger, ezClip, RightSideUp, Hovervue, NameTag, NameTray, Uptime 2000, and a quick version of Space Invaders.
Web Only one still up is GuitarTube.org. Some others that are no longer around are Roomdash (GitHub repo) and Countdowns.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>